Guide to the Communications Workers of America Records Addendum WAG.124.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Files of Vice-President John C. Carroll, 1958-1992.
  - Union-wide Staff Meeting (I), Feb 1978 (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - Union-wide Staff Meeting (II), Feb 1978 (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - United/Sprint, 1989-1991 (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - United/Sprint, 1991 (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - United/Sprint: Customer Agent Brochure, 1991 (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - United/Sprint: Flyers, 1990 (Box 137, Folder 7)
  - United/Sprint: Lawsuits, 1992 (Box 137, Folder 8)
  - United/Sprint: Media and Advertising, 1990 (Box 137, Folder 9)
  - United States Department of Labor: Grant Records, 1988 (Box 137, Folder 10)
  - United States Department of Labor Meeting, Sep 23, 1985 (Box 137, Folder 11)
  - US West, 1990 (Box 137, Folder 12)
  - US West-Bell Operating Companies: Negotiations with Sears and Radio Shack, 1985 (Box 137, Folder 13)
  - US West: Joint Committee, 1988 (Box 137, Folder 14)
  - US West: Occupational Job Evaluation (OJE), 1986 (Box 137, Folder 15)
  - Vacations, 1981 (Box 137, Folder 16)
  - Video Display Terminals (VDT), 1990 (Box 137, Folder 17)
  - Wage Data, 1981-1987 (Box 137, Folder 18)
  - Wage Differential Study (prepared by Development and Research Department), Jan 1977 (Box 137, Folder 19)
  - Wage Differential Study (Development and Research Department), Jun 1980 (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - Wage Differential Study (Development and Research Department), Nov 1985 (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Wage Incentive Plans, 1981-1986 (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - Wages, 1990 (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - Watson, Betty, 1988 (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - Western Electric Companies, 1973-1988 (Box 138, Folder 6)
  - Western Electric: Installation, 1980-1987 (Box 138, Folder 7)
  - Western Electric: Installation-Permanent Transfers, 1982 (Box 138, Folder 8)
  - Western Electric: Installation-Snow Grievances, 1966, 1979 (Box 138, Folder 9)
  - Western Electric: Manufacturing, 1980-1988 (Box 138, Folder 10)
  - Western Electric: Memorandum of Understanding, 1983 (Box 138, Folder 11)
  - Western Electric: Sales, 1981-1988 (Box 138, Folder 12)
  - Western Electric: Sales-Attendance Management System, 1979 (Box 138, Folder 13)
  - Western Electric: Wage incentive Plan, 1983 (Box 138, Folder 14)
  - West Virginia Newsletters, 1991 (Box 138, Folder 15)
  - Women, 1990 (Box 138, Folder 16)
  - Workers Rights, 1990 (Box 138, Folder 17)
  - Work Jurisdiction, 1976-1983 (Box 138, Folder 18)
  - Work Jurisdiction, 1986-1988 (Box 138, Folder 19)
  - Young Leaders Network, 1991 (Box 138, Folder 20)
- Series IV: The Correspondence of Lou Gerber, Legislative Staff, 1973-1982
  - Correspondence, Jan 1973-Apr 1973 (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, May 1973-Jul 1973 (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Aug 1973-Dec 1973 (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1974-Feb 1974 (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Mar 1974-Jul 1974 (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Aug 1974-Dec 1974 (Box 139, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1975-Apr 1975 (Box 139, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, May 1975-Aug 1975 (Box 139, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Sep 1975-Dec 1975 (Box 139, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 139, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1977-May 1977 (Box 139, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Jun 1977-Dec 1977 (Box 139, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1978-Jun 1978 (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Jul 1978-Dec 1978 (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1980-Aug 1980 (Box 140, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Sep 1980-Oct 1980 (Box 140, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Nov 1980-Dec 1980 (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1981-Mar 1981 (Box 140, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Apr 1981-Aug 1981 (Box 140, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Sep 1981-Dec 1981 (Box 140, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1982-Mar 1982 (Box 140, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Apr 1982-Aug 1982 (Box 140, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Sep 1982-Dec 1982 (Box 140, Folder 12)
- Series V: Files of John Morgan, Legislative Assistant to the President, 1966-1996
  - Subseries V:A: Correspondence, 1969-1994.
    - Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1973 (Box 141, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 141, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 141, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1976-Jul 1976 (Box 141, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Aug 1976-Dec 1976 (Box 141, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 141, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1978-May 1978 (Box 141, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Jun 1978-Dec 1978 (Box 141, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1979-May 1979 (Box 141, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Jun 1979-Dec 1979 (Box 141, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1980-Jul 1980 (Box 141, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, Aug 1980-Dec 1980 (Box 141, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1981-Jul 1981 (Box 141, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, Aug 1981-Dec 1981 (Box 141, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, Feb 1982-Jul 1982 (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Aug 1982-Dec 1982 (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1983-Jun 1983 (Box 142, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Jul 1983-Dec 1983 (Box 142, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 142, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 142, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence on 5" Disks (with printout of Document Titles), 1986 (Box 142, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 142, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 142, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1989-Jul 1989 (Box 142, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Sep 1989-Dec 1989 (Box 142, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1990-May 1990 (Box 142, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Jun 1990-Sep 1990 (Box 142, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, Oct 1990-Dec 1990 (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1991-Apr 1991 (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, May 1991-Jun 1991 (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Jul 1991-Aug 1991 (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, Sep 1991 (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Oct 1991 (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Nov 1991-Dec 1991 (Box 143, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1992 (Box 143, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Feb 1992 (Box 143, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Mar 1992 (Box 143, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Apr 1992-May 1992 (Box 143, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Jun 1992 (Box 143, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Jul 1992 (Box 143, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Aug 1992-Sep 1992 (Box 143, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, Oct 1992 (Box 143, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, Nov 1992 (Box 143, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, Dec 1992 (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1993-Feb 1993 (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Mar 1993 (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Apr 1993 (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, May 1993-Jun 1993 (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Jul 1993-Aug 1993 (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Sep 1993-Oct 1993 (Box 144, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Nov 1993-Dec 1993 (Box 144, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1994-Feb 1994 (Box 144, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Mar 1994-Apr 1994 (Box 144, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, May 1994-Jun 1994 (Box 144, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Jul 1994-Aug 1994 (Box 144, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Sep 1994-Oct 1994 (Box 144, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Nov 1994-Dec 1994 (Box 144, Folder 14)
  - Subseries V:B: Federal Communications Commission (FCC) Hearings, Rulings, and Court Cases, 1966-1995.
    - FCC: Computer Inquiry II, 1985 (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - FCC Hearings on American Broadcasting Company (ABC)-International Telephone and Telegraph (ITT) Merger (I), 1966-1967 (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - FCC Hearings on ABC-ITT Merger (II), 1966-1967 (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - FCC Hearings on American Telephone and Telegraph (AT&T) petition for Reclassification as Non-Dominant Carrier, 1995 (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - FCC Hearings on Bell System Procurement, 1978-1983 (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - FCC Hearings on Chesapeake and Potomac (C&P) Telephone Company Compliance Plan (I), 1990-1992 (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - FCC Hearings on C&P Telephone Company Compliance Plan (II), 1990-1992 (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - FCC Hearings on C&P Telephone Company Compliance Plan (III), 1990-1992 (Box 145, Folder 8)
    - FCC Hearings on C&P Telephone Company Compliance Plan (IV), 1990-1992 (Box 145, Folder 9)
    - FCC Hearings on C&P Telephone Company Compliance Plan (V), 1990-1992 (Box 145, Folder 10)
    - FCC Hearings on C&P Telephone Company Compliance Plan (VI), 1990-1992 (Box 145, Folder 11)
    - FCC Hearings on Citizens Utility Board (CUB), 1986 (Box 145, Folder 12)
    - FCC Hearings on Closed Captioning (Docket # 20693 RM-2616), 1975-1976 (Box 145, Folder 13)
    - FCC Hearings on Customer Premises Equipment, 1981-1985 (Box 145, Folder 14)
    - FCC Hearings on Divestiture-Job Loss, 1986 (Box 145, Folder 15)
    - FCC Hearings on Equal Access, 1984 (Box 145, Folder 16)
    - FCC Hearings on Foreign and Interstate Communications Service, 1968 (Box 145, Folder 17)
    - FCC Hearings on Foreign Trade-Sanyo (Korean Refrigerators), 1986-1987 (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - FCC Hearings on Inside Wiring, 1977-1985 (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - FCC Hearings on Inside Wiring (I), 1986 (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - FCC Hearings on Inside Wiring (II), 1986 (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - FCC Hearings on Inside Wiring, 1987-1988 (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - FCC Hearings on International Business Machines (IBM)/MCI Communications Corporation/Satellite Business Systems (SBS) transfer of Services, 1985-1986 (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - FCC Hearings on Joint Board (I), 1977-1984 (Box 146, Folder 7)
    - FCC Hearings on Joint Board (II), 1977-1984 (Box 146, Folder 8)
    - FCC Hearings on Joint Board (III), 1977-1984 (Box 146, Folder 9)
    - FCC Hearings on Joint Board (IV), 1977-1984 (Box 146, Folder 10)
    - FCC Hearings on Operator Service Rules, 1990-1991 (Box 146, Folder 11)
    - FCC Hearings on Petitions from Companies, 1983-1984 (Box 146, Folder 12)
    - FCC Hearings on Regulation of International Common Carrier Services, 1991 (Box 146, Folder 13)
    - FCC Hearings on Taxation of Telephone Concessions, 1985-1986 (Box 146, Folder 14)
    - FCC Hearings on Telecommunications Access for Disabled Persons, 1982-1983 (Box 146, Folder 15)
    - FCC Hearings on Telecommunications Access for Disabled Persons, 1984 (Box 146, Folder 16)
    - FCC Hearings on Telecommunications Access for Disabled Persons, 1985-1988 (Box 146, Folder 17)
    - FCC Hearings on Telecommunications Market Structure (I), 1966-1992 (Box 146, Folder 18)
    - FCC Hearings on Telecommunications Market Structure (II), 1966-1992 (Box 146, Folder 19)
    - FCC Hearings on Telecommunications Market Structure (III), 1966-1992 (Box 146, Folder 20)
    - FCC Hearings on Telecommunications Rates, 1968-1982 (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - FCC Hearings on Telecommunications Rates, 1983 (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - FCC Hearings on Telecommunications Rates, 1984-1986 (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - FCC v. AT&T-Proposed Split, 1984-1985 (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - FCC v. Ameritech, 1997 (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - FCC v. Dial-a-Porn Providers (Docket # 83-989), 1984-1990 (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - FCC v. ITT (Re: Maritime Mobile Service), 1984 (Box 147, Folder 7)
    - FCC v. ITT (Re: Removal of Service from Kennedy Airport), 1967 (Box 147, Folder 8)
    - FCC v. La Conexion Familiar, 1994 (Box 147, Folder 9)
    - FCC v. Metropolitan Fiber Systems Inc., 1990 (Box 147, Folder 10)
    - FCC v. Western Union (Docket # 17554-18270), 1968-1971 (Box 147, Folder 11)
  - Subseries V:C: Subject Files, 1973-1996
    - Anti-Dumping Laws, 1994-1996 (Box 147, Folder 12)
    - Anti-Trust Reform and Communications Reform Act (Brooks-Dingell Bill)-HR3626, 1993-1994 (Box 147, Folder 13)
    - Centre D`etudes des Systemes et des Technologies Avance'es (CESTA), 1985 (Box 147, Folder 14)
    - Chile: Trade Negotiations, 1995 (Box 147, Folder 15)
    - China: Most Favored Nation Trading Status, 1996 (Box 147, Folder 16)
    - Communications Act-S.1822 (I), 1994 (Box 147, Folder 17)
    - Communications Act-S.1822 (II), 1994 (Box 147, Folder 18)
    - Communications Act-S.1822 (III), 1994 (Box 147, Folder 19)
    - Communications Act-S.1822 (IV), 1994 (Box 147, Folder 20)
    - Communications Act-S.1822 (V), 1994 (Box 147, Folder 21)
    - Communications Act Amendment-S.2111, 1994 (Box 147, Folder 22)
    - Congressional Survey Summary, 1995 (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Congressional Symposium: The Role of Congress in Defining America's Trade Interests, Feb 24, 1995 (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - Deregulation, 1994 (Box 148, Folder 3)
    - FCC, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - FCC: Monitoring of Employees Telephones, 1973 (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - Gephardt, Richard: Trade Policy, 1996 (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - Intellectual Property, 1996 (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - Internet, 1994 (Box 148, Folder 8)
    - Japan: Auto Talks, 1995 (Box 148, Folder 9)
    - Japan Fair Trade Commission: U.S. Government, 1995 (Box 148, Folder 10)
    - Labor/Industry Coalition for International Trade (LICIT)/Coalition for Open Trade (COT), 1996 (Box 148, Folder 11)
    - LICIT/COT-Ex-Im Bank-Helping Keep America Competitive, 1996 (Box 148, Folder 12)
    - LICIT/COT-Implementing the Uruguay Round and Dealing with Japan, 1994 (Box 148, Folder 13)
    - LICIT/COT-Luncheon/Meeting, 1996 (Box 148, Folder 14)
    - Minnesota Rate Case, 1981 (Box 148, Folder 15)
    - North American Agreement on Labor Cooperation Report, 1996 (Box 148, Folder 16)
    - North American Free Trade Agreement, 1996 (Box 148, Folder 17)
    - Primary Instrument Concept (PIC) Proceedings (I), 1978 (Box 148, Folder 18)
    - PIC Proceedings (II), 1978 (Box 148, Folder 19)
    - PIC Proceedings (III), 1978 (Box 148, Folder 20)
    - Regional Bell Operating Companies (RBOC)-Counter Proposals, 1994 (Box 148, Folder 21)
    - Summit of the Americas, 1994 (Box 148, Folder 22)
    - Telecommunications Legislation-Correspondence, Press Releases and Testimony, 1991 (Box 148, Folder 23)
    - Telecommunications Legislation-Correspondence, Press Releases and Testimony, 1993 (Box 148, Folder 24)
    - Telecommunications Legislation-Correspondence, Press Releases and Testimony, 1994 (Box 148, Folder 25)
    - Teleport Communications, 1992 (Box 148, Folder 26)
    - Teleport Communications, 1993 (Box 148, Folder 27)
    - Television Viewers of America (TVA), 1994 (Box 148, Folder 28)
    - Trade Deficit, 1996 (Box 148, Folder 29)
    - Trade Deficit: The Trade Picture, Year End 1995, 1996 (Box 148, Folder 30)
    - US Department of Labor: Secretary of Labor, 1996 (Box 148, Folder 31)
    - United States: Pacific Trade and Investment Policy Commission, 1996 (Box 148, Folder 32)
    - United States: Regulation of Communications Industry, 1979-1983 (Box 148, Folder 33)
    - United States Trade Representative, 1994-1996 (Box 148, Folder 34)
    - Universal Service, 1994 (Box 148, Folder 35)
    - World Trade Organization (WTO), 1996 (Box 148, Folder 36)
    - WTO Negotiations: Labor/Industry Coalition for International Trade (LICIT), 1996 (Box 148, Folder 37)
    - WTO Negotiations: Uruguay Round, 1994 (Box 148, Folder 38)
    - WTO Negotiations: Uruguay Round-Final Act, 1994 (Box 148, Folder 39)
- Series VI: Files of the Contract Compliance Section, 1971-1995.
  - Alltel Incorporated, 1992-1994 (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - Alltel of Alabama, Inc., 1986-1995 (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Alltel of Carolina, Inc., 1991-1993 (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Alltel of Elyria, Inc., 1981-1991 (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Alltel of Florida, Inc., 1989-1992 (Box 149, Folder 5)
  - Alltel of Illinois, Inc., 1984-1990 (Box 149, Folder 6)
  - Alltel of Michigan, Inc., 1980-1990 (Box 149, Folder 7)
  - Alltel of Mississippi, Inc., 1984-1987 (Box 149, Folder 8)
  - Alltel of Mississippi, Inc., 1990-1993 (Box 149, Folder 9)
  - Alltel of Ohio, Inc., 1986-1989 (Box 149, Folder 10)
  - Alltel of Pennsylvania, Inc., 1986-1992 (Box 149, Folder 11)
  - Alltel of South Carolina, Inc., 1990 (Box 149, Folder 12)
  - American Telephone and Telegraph (AT&T): Business Units (I), 1989-1990 (Box 149, Folder 13)
  - AT&T: Business Units (II), 1989-1990 (Box 149, Folder 14)
  - AT&T: Customer Support and Operations Division #2 (I), 1989 (Box 149, Folder 15)
  - AT&T: Customer Support and Operations Division #2 (II), 1989 (Box 149, Folder 16)
  - AT&T: DC-14 (I), 1989 (Box 149, Folder 17)
  - AT&T: DC-14 (II), 1989 (Box 149, Folder 18)
  - AT&T: Federal Systems, 1989 (Box 149, Folder 19)
  - AT&T: Goddard Distribution Center-Salaried Clerical, 1990 (Box 149, Folder 20)
  - AT&T: Installation/CARA, 1989 (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - AT&T: Intelligent Network Services Business Unit, 1990-1991 (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - AT&T: Long Lines Department, 1971 (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - AT&T: Manufacturing (I), 1990-1998 (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - AT&T: Manufacturing (II), 1989-1990 (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - AT&T: Manufacturing (III), 1989-1990 (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - AT&T: Material Management Services (I), 1989 (Box 150, Folder 7)
  - AT&T: Material Management Services (II), 1989 (Box 150, Folder 8)
  - AT&T: New River Valley Plant, 1990 (Box 150, Folder 9)
  - AT&T: Operations Support Center (I), 1989 (Box 150, Folder 10)
  - AT&T: Operations Support Center (II), 1989 (Box 150, Folder 11)
  - ATTIS/IBEW, 1986 (Box 150, Folder 12)
  - Ameritech Applied Technologies (I), 1990 (Box 150, Folder 13)
  - Ameritech Applied Technologies (II), 1990 (Box 150, Folder 14)
  - Ameritech Publishing-Michigan, 1990 (Box 150, Folder 15)
  - Ameritech Publishing-Ohio, 1990 (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - Ameritech Services, 1989 (Box 151, Folder 2)
  - Bell Laboratories, 1974-1976 (Box 151, Folder 3)
  - Bell Laboratories, 1989 (Box 151, Folder 4)
  - Bell South, 1989-1991 (Box 151, Folder 5)
  - Bell South Services, 1986-1987 (Box 151, Folder 6)
  - Brrooksville/Murraysville Telephone Company, 1988 (Box 151, Folder 7)
  - Carolina Telephone Company, 1994 (Box 151, Folder 8)
  - Central Telephone Company (Centel) of Illinois, 1981-1990 (Box 151, Folder 9)
  - Centel of Illinois, 1993 (Box 151, Folder 10)
  - Centel of Minnesota, 1981-1990 (Box 151, Folder 11)
  - Centel of North Carolina, 1989-1990 (Box 151, Folder 12)
  - Centel of Ohio, 1987-1990 (Box 151, Folder 13)
  - Centel of Ohio, 1991-1994 (Box 151, Folder 14)
  - Centel of Texas, 1989-1990 (Box 151, Folder 15)
  - Centel of Virginia, 1989-1990 (Box 151, Folder 16)
  - Centel of Virginia, 1993 (Box 151, Folder 17)
  - Chautaugua and Erie Telephone Company, 1991 (Box 151, Folder 18)
  - Chesapeake and Potomac (C&P) Telephone Company, 1974-1976 (Box 151, Folder 19)
  - C&P Telephone Company, 1986-1988 (Box 151, Folder 20)
  - C&P Telephone Company, 1989 (Box 151, Folder 21)
  - Cincinnati Bell, 1974 (Box 151, Folder 22)
  - Citizens Utilities, 1994 (Box 151, Folder 23)
  - Commonwealth Telephone, 1994 (Box 151, Folder 24)
  - Continental Telephone Company (Contel): Data Services, 1989 (Box 151, Folder 25)
  - Contel of Alabama, 1984-1993 (Box 151, Folder 26)
  - Contel of California, 1989 (Box 151, Folder 27)
  - Contel of Missouri, 1989-1992 (Box 151, Folder 28)
  - Contel of New York, 1985-1991 (Box 151, Folder 29)
  - Contel of South Dakota, 1989 (Box 151, Folder 30)
  - Contel of the West: Arizona, 1993 (Box 151, Folder 31)
  - Contel of the West: Mountain West Division, 1989 (Box 151, Folder 32)
  - Contel of Virginia, 1984-1990 (Box 151, Folder 33)
  - Contel of West Virginia, 1990 (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - Diamond State Telephone Company, 1986-1988 (Box 152, Folder 2)
  - Diamond State Telephone Company, 1989 (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - Florence Telephone Company, 1981-1984 (Box 152, Folder 4)
  - General Telephone Company (GTE) of Alabama, 1993-1994 (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - GTE of Arkansas, 1990-1993 (Box 152, Folder 6)
  - GTE of California, 1986-1989 (Box 152, Folder 7)
  - GTE of California, 1991-1994 (Box 152, Folder 8)
  - GTE of Indiana, 1991 (Box 152, Folder 9)
  - GTE of Iowa, 1991-1993 (Box 152, Folder 10)
  - GTE of Kentucky, 1991 (Box 152, Folder 11)
  - GTE of Missouri, 1990-1994 (Box 152, Folder 12)
  - GTE of North Carolina, 1991-1995 (Box 152, Folder 13)
  - GTE of Ohio, 1990-1994 (Box 152, Folder 14)
  - GTE of the Midwest: Missouri Division, 1989 (Box 152, Folder 15)
  - GTE of the North: Indiana Division, 1990 (Box 152, Folder 16)
  - GTE of the North: Iowa-Nebraska Division, 1989 (Box 152, Folder 17)
  - GTE of the North: Pennsylvania Division, 1993 (Box 152, Folder 18)
  - GTE of the North: Wisconsin-Operations, 1992 (Box 152, Folder 19)
  - GTE of the Northwest, 1986-1993 (Box 152, Folder 20)
  - GTE of the Northwest: Idaho Division, 1989 (Box 152, Folder 21)
  - GTE of the South: Alabama Division, 1989 (Box 152, Folder 22)
  - GTE of the South: Georgia Division, 1990 (Box 152, Folder 23)
  - GTE of the South: Kentucky Division, 1990-1993 (Box 152, Folder 24)
  - GTE of the South: West Virginia-Virginia Division, 1989 (Box 152, Folder 25)
  - GTE of the South: West Virginia-Virginia Division, 1993 (Box 152, Folder 26)
  - GTE of the Southeast: Durham Toll Center, 1989-1990 (Box 152, Folder 27)
  - GTE of the Southwest, 1994 (Box 152, Folder 28)
  - GTE of the Southwest: Texas Division, 1989 (Box 152, Folder 29)
  - GTE of Wisconsin, 1990 (Box 152, Folder 30)
  - GTEL, 1990 (Box 152, Folder 31)
  - Illinois Bell, 1971-1972 (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - Illinois Bell, 1974 (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - Illinois Bell (I), 1986 (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - Illinois Bell (II), 1986 (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Illinois Bell, 1987-1988 (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Illinois Bell (I), 1989 (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - Illinois Bell (II), 1989 (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - Indiana Bell, 1971 (Box 153, Folder 8)
  - Indiana Bell, 1974-1975 (Box 153, Folder 9)
  - Indiana Bell (I), 1986-1987 (Box 153, Folder 10)
  - Indiana Bell (II), 1986-1987 (Box 153, Folder 11)
  - Indiana Bell (I), 1989 (Box 153, Folder 12)
  - Indiana Bell (II), 1989 (Box 153, Folder 13)
  - Kingdom Telephone Company, 1992 (Box 153, Folder 14)
  - Malheur Home Telephone Company, 1971 (Box 153, Folder 15)
  - Mark Twain Rural Telephone Company, 1991-1994 (Box 153, Folder 16)
  - Michigan Bell, 1974-1976 (Box 153, Folder 17)
  - Michigan Bell (I), 1986-1987 (Box 153, Folder 18)
  - Michigan Bell (II), 1986-1987 (Box 153, Folder 19)
  - Michigan Bell (I), 1989 (Box 153, Folder 20)
  - Michigan Bell (II), 1989 (Box 153, Folder 21)
  - Michigan Bell Communications, 1987 (Box 153, Folder 22)
  - Michigan Bell Communications, 1989 (Box 153, Folder 23)
  - Mid-Michigan Telephone Corporation, 1982 (Box 153, Folder 24)
  - Mountain Bell, 1971-1972 (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - Mountain Bell, 1974-1976 (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - Mountain States Telephone (I), 1986 (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - Mountain States Telephone (II), 1986 (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - Mountain States Telephone, 1987-1989 (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - New England Telephone and Telegraph: Central Order Bureau, 1986 (Box 154, Folder 6)
  - New England Telephone and Telegraph: Directory-Clerical, 1972 (Box 154, Folder 7)
  - New England Telephone and Telegraph: Directory-Sales, 1971 (Box 154, Folder 8)
  - New England Telephone and Telegraph: Letter of Understanding, 1976 (Box 154, Folder 9)
  - New England Telephone and Telegraph: New Hamphshire-Commercial, 1986 (Box 154, Folder 10)
  - New Jersey Bell, 1971-1972 (Box 154, Folder 11)
  - New Jersey Bell, 1986-1987 (Box 154, Folder 12)
  - New Jersey Bell, 1989 (Box 154, Folder 13)
  - New Jersey Bell: Letters of Agreement, 1974-1976 (Box 154, Folder 14)
  - New Jersey Telephone Company, 1982 (Box 154, Folder 15)